sousa kanashimi wo yasashisa ni jibun rashisa wo chikara ni
turn your sadness into kindness, your uniqueness into strength
mayoinagarademo ii arukidashite
even if you get lost, let's start walking
mou ikkai
one more time
dareka no kitai ni zutto kotae
are you really happy
homerarerunoga suki nano desuka
when you're always meeting to someone's expectations?
naritai jibun wo surikaetemo
even if you change to who you really wanna be
egao wa itsudemo suteki desuka
will you always have a great smile?
hajimaridake yume mite okiru
dreaming of only the beginning, I wake up
sono saki nara itsuka jibun no ude de
and someday, I'll live on my own.
souda daiji na mono wa itsumo katachi no nai mono dake
yes, precious things are never in shape
te ni iretemo nakushitemo kizukanumama
you never know what it is when you get it or lose it
sousa kanashimi wo yasashisa ni jibun rashisa wo chikara ni
turn your sadness into kindness, your uniqueness into strength
mayoinagarademo ii arukidashite
even if you get lost, let's start walking
mou ikkai
one more time
Sakura!
It was worth teaching you Genjutsu
in survival training
during the Genin Exam.
You truly have a talent for it.
Huh?
Release the Genjutsu and
wake up Naruto and Shikamaru!
Naruto will be delighted.
He'll be getting a mission
after such a long while.
What do you mean by a mission?
Be careful...
It's the first A-Ranked mission
since the Land of the Waves.
I've Been Waiting
For
This!
It's an A-Rank Mission!!
Sensei! What do you mean by A-Ranked
mission in the condition we are in?!
What do we have to do?!
Sasuke is chasing Gaara and company
of the Sand Village.
Sakura...
Release the Genjutsu
on Naruto and Shikamaru,
and go after Sasuke.
I feel uneasy...
about that unusual Chakra.
But then,
we should wake up Ino and Choji
and go in a large group.
There may already
be quite a large number
of Sand and Sound Shinobi
who have infiltrated this village.
Actions lose quickness when there's more
than the fundamental four in a squad...
and it becomes difficult to
hide from the enemy.
You learned that in the Academy's
patrol practical training, right?
Oh, I see! Then four means
that you'll come with us...
No, I must not leave here.
Summoning Jutsu!
As for the rest, this Pakkun will
track down Sasuke by scent!
C-Could it be...
the one other member is this puppy?!
Hey! Little girl!
Don't you be calling me a cute puppy!
I didn't say... cute.
Okay, Sakura! Release the Genjutsu
on Naruto and Shikamaru!
Okay!
Release!
What is it... Sakura-chan?
Get down!
I'll tell you later!
Just stay down!
Shikamaru... you were...
from the beginning...
Ouch!
You were able to release Genjutsu, too!
Why were you pretending
to be asleep?!
Humph! I don't want to
end up getting involved!
Hell no...
I couldn't care less about Sasuke!
Ouch!
W-What's going on...?
Naruto! Behind you!
F-Fast...
Not just fast...
Guy-sensei!
Now, I'll announce the mission!
As soon as you've heard what
the mission is, go through that hole.
Track down Sasuke,
join up and then stop him!
Then await next orders
in a safe place.
Huh? Did something happen
to Sasuke?!
I'll tell you the reason en route!
Let's go!
Jeez... Why me?
Hey, boy!
Huh...?
If this mission is a success,
as a reward I'll let you
touch my paw-pads.
So don't sulk like that!
Huh?
See?
They're soft and supple!
Su... pple...?
Yes, very...
Soft and supple!
Let's just go!
H-Hey!
Will it be okay with just them?
They'll be okay.
Pakkun is with them.
As long as they don't pursue too far...
To think I'd be able to fight you again...
This barrier can't be broken
unless it's from the inside.
If Hokage-sama would just
take out one of those four,
we could help...
Hey, it's gonna start soon.
Put up a barrier on the inside, too!
Sure!
Hm... It doesn't look like
I'll be able to get out this easily.
You don't really mean that.
It'd be tougher for you if someone
came in and got in the way, right?
Ninja Art: Tile Shuriken!
That's too easy!
Striking Shadow Snake!
With such a weak technique...
It sucks to get old, eh,
Sarutobi-sensei?
Substitution?!
Earth Style: Great Mud River!
Is this it?
I don't think so!
Earth Style: Earth Dragon Bomb!
Fire Dragon Bomb!
He's combined Earth and Fire!
Excellent, Hokage-sama!
Stop the stupid act, Orochimaru.
Very good...
Really, I've been grossly underestimated.
Did you think you could kill me
with that level of Jutsu?
Humph... A hateful fellow as usual!
Don't say that.
A high maintenance student is cute.
Right, Sarutobi-sensei?
Something's strange...
All of the Academy's classes
doing self-study.
And that smoke...
That's coming from the direction
of the exam arena.
Isn't there some disturbance
to the east?
I wonder if something happened...
This is definitely strange!
But sudden self-study is
sure a smack in the eye!
It's been like this for a while!
Yeah. Iruka-sensei
and everyone are late...
Aren't they, Konohamaru-kun?
Konohamaru-kun?
Yikes!
Jeez, what is this?!
And Mom just bought this for me!
I'll loan you my colored pencil.
What're you saying?!
This color is this spring's new color!
Aww, what'll I do?
That is...?
I wonder if Naruto-kun and the others
went to stop Sasuke-kun?
Those brats?
But surely, some Genin won't
be able to make any difference...
Hm? Is this the data of
that kid back there?
You give him too much credit.
Think again!
You'll trip up if you underestimate him.
"Teachers' Office"
There is information that several units
have already infiltrated the village...!
We should evacuate the students
to a safe place right away!
Yes... And without causing panic
among the students!
Then let's evacuate the students
as soon as possible under
the pretense of an evacuation drill!
Isn't it about time
we stopped playing around?
This isn't an Academy class, so...
You have a point.
Did you foresee your final moments?
I won't go easy on you
just because you're senile.
I look forward to it.
Depending on your Jutsu,
I might have to have you
start over at the Academy!
Please don't disappoint me too much!
W-Wow...
What Chakra?!
Yeah... It seems the air is
bearing down within the body!
Shuriken Shadow Clone Jutsu!
Summoning Jutsu: Reanimation!
That technique!
One!
He is using a Summoning Jutsu
as a shield.
And this dead person is...
Two!
I must stop the third one at any cost...!
Three!
It looks like the third one was no good.
Oh well...
It looks like I stopped the third one.
Now, this is where it gets tough...
He summoned those two of all people...
I-It can't be!
Those personages are...!
Those personages are?
Now, what will you do,
Sarutobi-sensei...?
No...
Third... Hokage-sama.
Okay! Everyone, please move quickly!
Oh, what a day!
My favorite colored pencil
didn't have to break like that!
Lousy evacuation drill...
Self-study was better.
Konohamaru-chan's been quiet, hasn't he?
I wonder what's wrong?
Huh? Yeah.
After the whole school does
a long self-study,
the whole school does
an evacuation drill.
This is too strange!
Okay! Stop! Get in line!
That look on Iruka-sensei's face...
Something's definitely going on here!
And also...
Okay, everyone!
Don't go off on your own.
That rainbow... It's been
bugging me for a while!
What's that, Old Man?
There's a strange rainbow!
It's an unusual rainbow!
Do you like rainbows, Konohamaru?
Yeah! And I've never seen
such a pretty rainbow!
I see, I see.
But, Konohamaru...
Hmm?
Rainbows used to symbolize snakes...
And it's said that they bode evil.
Such a pretty thing? That's a lie!
I see, I see.
Symbolizes snakes...
Is something happening?
Long time no see... Saru.
Oh, it's you...
You've gotten old, Sarutobi.
I never thought I would meet
the great brothers in this manner...
It's regretful.
This is bad.
That Summoning Jutsu...
Who in the world are they?!
Please prepare yourselves...
First Hokage-sama...
Second Hokage-sama!
That's right...
The one with the black hair
is the First Hokage.
The one with the white hair
is the Second Hokage.
They are both reputed to
be the highest Shinobi
and they are the Hokage
who built the today's Leaf Village!
Reanimation, huh?
This youth summoned us with
the Forbidden Jutsu, then?
He's something else...
Then, Sarutobi!
Does this mean we must... fight you?
Let's stop the old people
get-together talk...
Shall we get started?
There's always fighting...
no matter when you live.
You like that, don't you?
No good will come by deriding the dead
and playing around with time!
I get it! So that's what happened!
That Sasuke, getting all impatient!
So, why am I pulled into this?!
This is such a drag!
It can't be helped!
It's Kakashi-sensei's order.
This way!
That brat, huh...
Let's go!
dare datte shippai wa surunda hazukashii koto janai
everyone makes mistakes it's nothing to be ashamed about
kono kizu o muda ni shinai de waratte arukereba ii
don't let this scar be for naught walk with a smile
sou shizuka na kuuki suikomi hiroki sora ni kao age tobikomi
yes, breathe in the air and lift your face to the sky and jump
toki ni ame ga futtara hito yasumi jaa yukusaki wa kaze fuku mama ni
if it rains, take a break go where the wind takes you
takusan no matotteru koukai kono kizu o muda ni shicha shounai
so many regrets don't let this scar be for naught
ude ni kunshou kizami ikoukai shougai
let's go carve the in our chest
sou kokkara ga SHOW TIME
yes, it's show time, life begins now.
dare datte shippai wa surunda hazukashii koto janai
everyone makes mistakes It's nothing to be ashamed about
kono kizu o muda ni shinai de waratte arukereba ii
don't let this scar be for naught walk with a smile
kanashimi mo kaze ni kaete tsuyoku susunde ikereba ii
transform sadness into the wind and continue to forge on
tsuyoku susunde ikereba ii
forge on strong
Damn it! The pursuer is too fast!
Once we Genin get caught,
that will be the end.
In that case,
we should ambush and attack them.
I already thought of it,
but it'll probably be no use.
Then, what should we do?!
There is only one choice.
Next time:
"Coward No 1. It's Troublesome, But I've Got to Do It!!"
It isn't my style,
but we have no choice, I guess.